------------------OP-----------------------------
---------------------------------------------------------------------
樱律联萌站 http://bbs.ylbud.com/
樱律联萌站为您带来高质量中日双语字幕
真奥さん
中日双语字幕由 樱律字幕组 制作
ちーちゃん
俺、エンテイスラに帰らなきゃならない
Mr. Maou...
感谢以下成员倾情制作
听译：五月、吉禾、兔走之　校对：深雪　时间轴：咲夜　后期：OMG
Chi... I have to go back to Ente Isla.
そんな、嫌です
私、分かれたくはありません
Oh, no... I don't want you to!
I don't want us to be separated!
ごめん、だけどこれ以上
この世界に逗まれない
------------------ED-----------------------------
だったら、私もエンテイスラに行きます
I'm sorry. But I can't stay
in this world any longer.
つれて行ってください
それだけは、できない
Then I'll go to Ente Isla, too!
Please take me with you!
俺たちは元々
別の世界に住むもの
That, I can't do.
出会うべきじゃなかった
By rights, you and I live in different worlds.
We should never have met.
ちーちゃん
ごめんな
Chi. I'm sorry.
真奥さん
Mr. Maou...
Mr. Maou!
という夢を見ました
終わる
エンテイスラに帰る夢ね
And that was my dream! The end.
って、私はその後
どうなるの
A dream where I go back to Ente Isla, eh?
So, what happens to me next?
どうなるって
Huh? After that?
それは、その
まぁ、何でもいいけど
今の俺には無理だな
Well, you...
そんな魔力残ってないし
Well, whatever. I can't go now anyway.
しかし
昨日は疲れた
I don't have enough magic left.
Man, yesterday was exhausting!
あれから壊れたビルを修復して
After the fight I had to
restore all the broken buildings...
おまけにゲートにサリエルを放り込んで
全部魔力使っちまったからな
Not to mention open a Gate
and toss Sariel through it.
ほー
ちーちゃん
真君は
I used up all my magic!
はい
河内から聞いたぞ
I see...
Hey Chi, where's Maa?
昨日の夜モップを持って
Here!
飛び出して行ったきり
Kawa-cchi told me.
戻ってこなかったそうじゃないか
You grabbed a mop and ran out
last night, and you never came back?
それは
ちょっといろいろありまして
何でちーちゃんまで
Ah, well, you see...
貞夫殿は
There were some circumstances...
私達を助けてくれたのだ
Why are you making excuses too?
どうも
The good Sadao saved us last night.
クレスティア·ベル
Good evening.
魔王の店に行ってるみたいだね
いくら監視のためとはいえ
Looks like Crestia Bel's
visiting Maou's restaurant.
いい加減覗きは趣味が悪
Your voyeurism is in very poor taste,
even if it is for surveillance pur...
エミリァだけでなく
ベルにも発信機を付けたんだな
一体いくらした
So you didn't stop at Emilia...
you planted a tracker on Bel, too!
ちょっと泡だらけの手で触らないでよ
失礼ですが
How much did it cost?!
Hey, don't touch me with soapy hands.
鎌月铃乃
昨夜千穂殿と一緒に帰宅する途中
Excuse me, but...
My name is Suzuno Kamazuki.
偏執者に追われているところを
Good Chiho and I were attacked by
a deviant last night on our way home,
貞夫殿が助けに駆けつけてくれたのだ
そ、そうなんです
真奥さんが来てくれなかったら
and the good Sadao rushed to our aid.
私達にどうなってたか
Y-Yes, he did! I don't know what
would've happened to us if not for him!
モップで撃退したか
えーちょっと手強い奴でして
You fought him off with a mop?
そういうことなら、仕方ないな
Y-Yes, he was a bit of a tough customer...
失礼します
木崎さん、冷蔵庫から人が
Well, I suppose that counts
as extenuating circumstances.
Excuse me! Miss Kisaki, a man
came out of the refrigerator!
サリエル
ゲートに追放したんじゃありませんでしだっけ
貞夫殿、これはもしや
- Who is this guy?
- Sariel?!
- Beats me. He does seem to be alive, but...
- I thought you ejected him through the Gate?
あの笹飾りが魔王の魔力に効して
- Better call an ambulance, I guess.
- Good Sadao, perhaps the bamboo
ornaments responded to the Devil's magic
ゲートの出口をこの店の中に出現させたのでは
- You guess?
- Good Sadao, perhaps the bamboo
ornaments responded to the Devil's magic
- Yeah, I don't want to stir up too much trouble...
- Good Sadao, perhaps the bamboo
ornaments responded to the Devil's magic
by opening the Gate's
exit inside the restaurant?
気づいた
大丈夫か
死んでないか
美しい
Oh, he's awake.
は
何という運命
You okay? Not dead or anything?
僕は異世界で美の女神と巡り合った
Beautiful.
Huh?
How strange is fortune! In another world,
I have met the goddess of beauty!
神よ、僕は禁断の恋に漕がれて
堕天使の落ちようとしています
O goddess, so desperate am I for thy
forbidden love that I may fall from Heaven!
何だ、この馬鹿は
実はその
向かいのセンダッキ
Who is this idiot?
ォー　我が愛しの君を
Actually, he's from the
Sentucky across the street...
マクとセンタ決して相容れのない
My beloved! You from MgR's and I from
SFC, two irreconcilable organizations,
組織に身を置く私と貴方は
正しくファーストフード界のロミオとジュリエットと
頭の落ちどころでも悪かったか
are the very Romeo and Juliet
of the fast-food industry!
救急車を呼んだほうがいいようだな
Did that fall damage your brain?
I really should call an ambulance.
なんとやさしい言葉
私の身を案じてくれているのですね
Oh, such kind words!
You are concerned for my health.
しかし、例えどんな医術を持ってしても
この恋の病は治せない
But no miracle of medicine
can cure this lovesick heart!
痛っ　痛っ
どうやら警察の方がいいみたいだ
これが堕天の誘惑
So you'd rather I call the police!
なんと言う、甘美の欝気
This is what tempts angels to fall!
Oh, what sweet agony!
この瞬間
在这瞬间
この場所がスダート
这里就是起点
イメージして見よう
试着想象一下
Right here, this moment,
this is our starting point
何ができるのかな
我能做些什么
Let's picture what we might be able to do
信じられない出来事だってある
会发生些不可思议的事吧
もっと超えて行けるね
克服一切走的更远
Unbelievable things can happen sometimes
More... we can push past this
ゼロから生まれるすべて輝いて
从零重生的一切都特别耀眼
FLYあの空へ
翱翔朝着那片天空
Everything is born from zero;
I want to shine, flap my wings hard
思い切り羽ばたきたい
想尽情地展翅
最高のスマイルで笑いながら
以最完美的笑容
And fly to that sky
さぁ、行く
笑着前行吧
Come on, let's go, with
brilliant smiles on our faces!
未知の世界へと　今飛び出そうよ
奔向未知的世界仿佛就要飞出来
Let's fly off to an unknown world right now
未来を選び決めるのは自分
自己决定自己的未来
夢を追いかけて行　こう泣く日をある
追逐着梦想前进　也会有哭泣的日子
I decide, I'm the one who chooses my future
それは大事な願い消えないで
珍贵的愿望不会消失
Let's follow our dreams
Sure, some days we'll cry
It's a precious wish, don't disappear
きっと会えるから
一定可以再次遇
明日の君
朝着未来的你
I'm going after the future you,
because I know I'll find you
"The Devil is a Part-Timer!"
The Devil and the Hero
Do Some Honest Hard Work
魔王と勇者、真っ当に仕事に励む
Again, my name is Yusa, and I thank you
for allowing me to assist you today.
はい、ありがとうございました
本日は遊佐がうかがいました
What's going on?
What is this?
どういうこと
これは
I rule over Hatagaya at last!
Now for my next conquest... Greenland!
俺はつい幡ヶ谷を支配した
Say what?
次はいよいよグリーンランドだ
What a messed-up dream...
Well, I doubt MgR's will ever
be the new Devil's Castle,
何って夢
but I still can't let my guard down.
まぁ、さすがにマグドが
魔王城になるようなことがないだろうけど
Emi, you seem kinda fired up today.
まだまだ油断は禁物よね
I-I guess so.
So, want to go get dinner together?
恵美、なんか気合い入ってるね
Sorry, I can't today.
まあね
You're going to go check on Mr. Maou again?
どう、今日はこれから晩御飯でも一緒に
Not "check on" so much as "keep tabs on"...
ごめん、今日はちょっと
Seriously? Don't you think it's time
you two let go of hard feelings?
まだ真奥さんの様子を見に行くの
様子っていうか
監視っていうか
Not possible.
いい加減、二人ども
そういう蟠りは捨ててもいい時期何じゃない
I mean, it's just complicated, you know?
無理よ
"Sasazuka Station"
まぁ、いろいろといろいろなのよ
My village... my father was killed.
There's no way I could ever forgive that.
村を、父を殺されたのよ
Or would...? No, anyway,
I'm a hero and he's the Devil!
決して許せるわけがない
それども
And there's no telling when he might
turn enemy again, like in my dream.
そもそも、私は勇者で
Sadao
Maou
アイツは魔王なのよ
あの夢のように
I'm coming in!
何時また牙を剥くか
分からないし
What are you doing?
Miss Yusa!
入るわよ
Miss Suzuno, what are you doing?!
何やってんのよ
Well, I made an attempt at French cooking,
遊佐さん
so I'm feeding him Udon
Confit with Sauce Américaine.
何やってんですか、鈴乃さん
いや、せっかくフランス料理に挑戦したので
What the heck is that?!
I already said I'd be making dinner today!
うどんのコンフィ ソーサー アメリケーヌも
And Mr. Maou, why are you
just going along with it?!
なんですか、そりゃ
夕飯は私が作るって言ったじゃないですか
Huh? But...
真奥さんも何でされるままになったんですか
Miss Suzuno, aren't you his
enemy in the first place?!
You're hand-feeding him like I want to!
えっ　えーやったてさぁ
Sasaki Chiho, you're letting
your true feelings show.
大体鈴乃さんは真奥さんの敵でしょう
You stay out of this, Mr. Urushihara.
相性だなんて羨ましいこと
Mr. Maou, whose dinner are you going
to eat? Mine, or Miss Suzuno's?!
佐々木千穂本音が出てる本音が
漆原さんは黙っててください
Ummmm...
真奥さん　私と鈴乃さんのご飯　どっちを食べるんですか
Budget-wise, it'd help if you took
turns bringing dinner every day...
え、家計的には
Oh, it's no big deal.
二人で交代で毎日ってのは助かるわけで
Th-That's right, no big deal!
This is the Devil?
いや、たいしたことではない
Sire.
そ　そうです　そうです
Y-Yo, Ashiya! Where have you been?!
これが真奥
I have grave business to discuss.
魔王様
Wh-Why the formality?
よ　芦屋どこ行ってたんだよ
I humbly request some leave time, Sire.
折り入ってお話が
何　何だよ改まって
"Nurls"
"Lizard Consommé Flavor"
What? Alciel visiting his home?
暫し　お暇をおいただきたく存じます
I really don't think he's returned to Ente Isla...
へ　アルシエルが里帰りですか
But Alciel himself said he wanted leave.
エンテイスランには戻ってきてないと思いますが
There are lots of types of vacations, though!
でも　アルシエル本人が暇をいただきたいって言ってたのよ
Maybe he's sick of that
cramped little Devil's Castle?
暇にもいろいろありますし
That definitely wasn't the
vibe I was getting, though.
狭い魔王城が嫌になったんじゃないでしょうか
"Leave time"? What's up?
どう考えてもそういう雰囲気じゃなかったけど
I'm afraid I can't speak of it here.
暇って　何だよ
Okay.
Sorry, could you three go home for today?
それは　ちょっとここでは
It sounds like Ashiya needs to talk to me.
分かった
悪い　今日のところは三人とも帰ってくれ
- All right.
- Okay...
Ah, yes, that does seem suspicious.
芦屋がなんか話しあるみたいだから
分かった　はい
なるほど　確かにそれは怪しいですね
Miss Emerada didn't know either?
No, although to be safe,
I'm having her sniff around
ェメラダさんに聞いても　分からなかったんですか
for anything suspicious happening in Ente Isla.
念のため　エンテイスランで何か
不審の動きがないか調べてもらったところなんだけど
We got caught in the rain.
降ってきちゃいましたね
Do you think Mr. Maou might
really go back to Ente Isla now?
ひょっとして真奥さん
本当にエンテイスランに帰っちゃうんじゃ
I'm afraid that dream might come true...
What did you dream about?
あの夢　やっぱり現実になるんじゃ
W-Well...
Come to think of it, I just
had an ominous dream too...
どんな夢を見たの
そ　それは
What? You too?
But don't worry.
そういえば　私も不吉な夢を見たとこなのね
I'll never let anything sad happen
to you while I'm around, Chiho.
へ　遊佐さんも
でも大丈夫　私がいる限り
千穂ちゃんには絶対に悲しい思いはさせたりはしないから
So many boxes... Did they go shopping?
No, they can't have that kind of money.
あんなにたくさんの荷物
何か買い物
Could that mean?
"Holyvitan β"
でもそんな経済的余裕はないはず
I got a package from Eme, so there's precedent.
ということ　まさか
Did they get something from the demon realm?!
エメに荷物を届けてもらった例もある
もし　もう魔界からなにか物資を
There really isn't anything strange going on!
I did have Albert look into it,
やっぱり　変わったことはないですね
Stop
Bidet-Back
(Soft)
but no unusual trouble's been reported!
一応　アルバートに調べてもらったんですけど
- Oh! But there is one problem!
- What?
目立ったトラブルの報告それで紛えん
I've gained a little weight recently!
あ　でも一つだけ困ったこたが
That's totally irrelevant!
何
最近　ちょっと太ってきたんですよね
Hmm? Emi, is that you? What are you doing?
それは関係ないでしょう
Oh, just thinking out loud!
うん　そんな声は恵美　何してるの
When I have surpassed you,
I shall come for you. - Mitsuki Sarue
What the hell is that dwarf manager thinking?
あ、ちょっと独り言
何を考えているんだ　あのちびこ店長は
Miss Kisaki.
I'm sorry for the short notice,
but I'd like you to switch my shifts.
うん 木崎さん　急で申し訳ないですけど
Hmm? That's unusual.
Sorry. Something's come up
that I can't get out of...
シフト変更してほしいんですが
うん　珍しいな
はあ、どうしても都合のつかないことがあって
Got it. I'll work something out.
Thank you, Ma'am!
うん　分かった　こっちでなんとか調整しよう
- Let me know when you need to be out.
- All right.
ありがとうございます
じゃ、シフトの変更日時を教えてくれ
Sheesh, rain again?
分かりました
Mr. Maou, are you going
home to Ente Isla after all?
あ　また雨かよ
That's why you're taking days off?!
Don't tell me you're never coming back...
やっぱり　真奥さん
エンテイスランに帰っちゃんですか　だから何休みをとって
Hold up! I don't have the magic to go home!
But... why, then?
まさかこのまま帰らないなんてこと
ちょっと　帰る魔力はねぇよ
I...
じゃ　だったらなんで
Sorry. I can't tell you.
それは　ごめん　理由は言えない
Mr. Maou...
真奥さん
Should we really do this?
いいんでしょうか　こんなことして
Wouldn't it be better to give
him the benefit of the doubt?
やっぱり真奥さんを信じてあげたほうが
I'd like to, but with the boxes and everything,
he's definitely plotting something.
そうしたいところだけと　この前の荷物といい
何か企んでいることは確かよ
Our only choice is to find out the truth.
真実を突き止めるしかない
- But...
- Shh!
でも
Now we tail him.
跡を付けるわよ
A construction site?
建設現場　ここに魔王城建設しようって計画
Is he planning to build
a new Devil's Castle here?
No, that's ridiculous.
そんなまさか
He's just working.
普通に働いてる
Why?
なんで
What are you up to?!
何やってんだよ
We needed money ASAP.
Gotta pay for two tracking devices.
早急に金が必要だったんだよ
発信機二つ分の支払いで
Tracking devices?!
発信機
Urushihara bought 'em.
漆原が買ったやつだ　お前の鞄と鈴乃の下駄につけてたんだよ
He planted 'em in your bag and Suzuno's sandals.
Wh-What?!
なん　なんですって
H-Hey! Stop! This is no place
to draw the sacred sword!
ほ　やめろう　こんなところで聖気を出すな
And they did help me find you guys
when Sariel kidnapped you, so...
おかげで　サリエに攫われた時は居場所が分かったんだし
For crying out loud!
あ、もう
Anyway, they're gonna debit
our account for those next week.
とにかく　そいつの代金引き落としは来週なんだよ
But there's no money in it.
And MgRonald's payday is after that.
でも　口座に金はねぇ　マグロナルドの給料日はまだ先
So Ashiya said, "In that case, I must
acquire a temp job that pays daily."
ならば　日払いの派遣のバイトをするしかないって
芦屋が言い出して
And that's why he asked for time off?
それでお暇をくださいって
Yep. So I decided to take
time off to work temp, too.
あ　で　おれもマクロナルド休ませてもらって是的 我也给麦丹劳请了假
"Please Use Caution"
働くことにしたんだ
The temp agency must've
sent Ashiya somewhere else.
芦屋も俺とは違うところに派遣されているはずだ
If that's all it was,
why'd you hide it from Chiho?
そんなことなら　どうして千穂ちゃんにも隠してたのよ
- Mm-hmm!
- Well, I... it's like...
まあ　その　なんだ　ちーちゃんに話したら
I was worried that if I told Chi,
she'd feel responsible
自分を助けるために使った発信機のお金ってことで
since the money's for the tracker
that helped me rescue her.
責任感じ違うかなって
I'm sorry, Chi!
すまん　ちーちゃん
I'm just glad you're not going
back to Ente Isla or anything.
でも　よかった
真奥さんがエンテイスランに帰るとかじゃなくて
So what's with the truckload of
boxes you had delivered, then?
それじゃ　この前届けられたあの大量の荷物は何
Say what? That's news to me, too.
あ　なんだ　それは俺も知らねぇぞ
Boxes?
荷物　何のことかな
Wh-What do you mean?
This stuff was here when I moved in.
これは僕がここに来る前からおいてあったものだし
Liar! We both know it wasn't.
嘘つけ　そんなものなかっただろろ　ちょっとそこどけ
Move over!
Feather beds...
羽毛布団　消火器　浄水器
Fire extinguishers...
Water purifiers...
And there's so many of them.
しかもこんなにたくさん
Urushihara. What the hell is this?
漆原なんなんだこれは
Well, like they say, you shouldn't
do stuff you don't understand.
いや、なれないことするもんじゃないね
I did some digging online, and it's
apparently called a "buy-up scam"...
後で調べたら　買い取り詐欺っていうやつらしくて
"Buy-up scam"?
買い取り詐欺
It's a ploy where someone comes to your door,
要らなくなったものを買うって家に押し掛け
says they'll buy your used stuff,
then fast-talks you into buying stuff.
うまいこと言って逆にものを買わせる手口よ
I sold him an external hard drive, but...
パソコンの外付けハードディスクを売ったんだけど
Then he kinda made me buy this...
そしたら代わりにこれを買わされちゃって
- How much? How much did it cost?
- So close, so close, so close...
いくら　いくらしたんだ
近い　近い
Um...
あの　12万8千円
128 thousand yen!
It seems you fell victim to
a very underhanded salesman.
どうやら　かなり悪質な業者にひかかってしまったようだな
Stupid sucker. Just turn those guys away!
世間知らずな　      追い返せよ
But I'm socially inept...
だって社会不適合者だし　僕
Satan, lecturing Lucifer now
won't accomplish anything.
真奥　今ここでルシヘフィルを責めても始まらん
This is the company, right?
ここがその会社ね
Deluxe Life International Holdings
We buy high, you get rich ! ! !
"Deluxe Life International Holdings"...
デラックス·ライフ　インターナショナル·ホールディングス
What's with the meaningless company name?
やな　その意味のない会社名は
Why not give them a call?
電話してみたら
Hello, this is Deluxe Life International Holdings.
はい
デラックス·ライ
フインターナショナル·ホールディングスでございます
How may I help you today?
本日はどのようなご要件でしょうか
The other day a door-to-door salesman
先日　訪問販売で羽毛布団と消火器と
sold us feather beds and fire
extinguishers and water purifiers,
浄水器を買ったんだけど
but we won't use them,
so we want to return them.
うちじゃ使わないから返品したいんだけど
I'm terribly sorry, Sir, but we run
water purifiers when we install them
大変申し訳にくいのですが
浄水器は取り付けの先に試しで水を流してしまっており
to make sure they work, so they're
essentially used, and can't be returned.
浄水に未使用といいがたく
返品はできかねます
We haven't used the twenty years'
worth of filters that came with them.
一緒についてきたフィルター20年分ってのは使ってないぞ
They come as a set with the purifiers,
so we're unable to refund just the filters.
あくまでセット料金となっておりますので
フィルターだけの返品は承りかねます
And as for the fire extinguishers,
once they've been installed,
あと　消火器に関しましても　消防法により
for safety reasons it's illegal
under the Fire Service Act
一度設置したものは安全上の問題から
for us to take them back, even unused.
たとえ未使用でも返品できかねますので
What about the feather beds, then?
それじゃ羽毛布団は？
We accept returns for those
as long as they're completely unused.
そちらに関しては完全未使用でしたら
お引取りいたします
You mean the set of seven, correct?
七組セットですね
No, it's a set of five.
いや　五組のはずだけど
I'm afraid our company only sells sets of seven.
こちらでは七組でしか売りしてないはずです
We can't accept sets that
are short any parts, so...
五組となると数が足りませんので
Just forget it!
もういい
They never intended to take any returns.
もともと返品なんか受ける気ないのよ
What should we do?!
どうします
- Negotiate in person?
- Negotiate in person!
直談判
So this is the place...
ここか
Coming!
はい
Ashiya?!
芦屋
Your Majesty?! And Emilia, too?!
魔王様　　エミリアまで
What brings you here?
どうしたんです
They gave you a temp job here?
お前の派遣先ってここだったのか？
That explains why the voice seemed so familiar.
道理で聞き覚えのある声かと
More to the point, what are you doing?
て言うかなにやってんのよ
Merely following the procedure for handling
unreasonable demands for returns...
私はただ
無理な返品を迫るクレーマーにマニュアルどおりの対応
No, wait! Why did he buy seven feather beds?!
待ってください
なぜ羽毛布団を七組も
I told you, he was duped!
And it wasn't seven, it was five.
だから騙されたんだって
それに七組じゃなくて五組だ
But that sounds like a scam!
それではまるで詐欺ではありませんか
That's what I've been tellin' you it was!
だからさっきから詐欺だっつってんだろうか
Then I've been sent here to
practice fraudulent business dealings,
すると私は悪徳企業に派遣され
and I've unwittingly acted as an agent of evil?!
知らないうちに悪の手先として
働かされていたというなのか
As I recall, you're a demon generalissimo.
悪の手先って言うか
悪魔大元帥よね
But now that I know, I cannot
remain here another second!
しかしそうと知ったからには
このような会社には一秒足りてもおられません
Quite the fuss over here.
騒がしいですね
S-Sir!
社長
Is there a problem?
どうかしましたか
Are you the jerk in charge?
てめぇが責任者か
Now, that's not nice! Why don't we
talk this over calmly, like adults?
口が悪いですね
冷静に話し合おうじゃありませんか
Sir, I'm sure this was
explained over the phone,
電話でお聞きになったとおもいますが
but it's all in the provisions of the contract.
契約書約款には書かれておりますので
Huh? What's this about "provisions"?
I didn't see any papers!
は　しらねぇよ　なんだよ　約款って
I gave you your copy. I really
must ask you to follow the rules.
お渡ししましたよ
困りますね　そんな適当じゃ
Excuse me? This is a scam!
なにいってんだ　こんなの詐欺でしょう
All participants consented to the deal, Sir.
合意の上で成り立った取引ですよ
"Consented," my butt!
何が合意だよ
Who'd be dumb enough to buy seven
feather beds for one rundown apartment?!
ボロアパートで羽毛布団七組買う馬鹿どこにいんだよ
A certain someone in your home.
お宅の部屋に一人
Y-You bastard, you're being smug
because you think we're clueless!
こ、この野郎
何もしらねぇと思って一気になりやがって
I didn't sell any defective goods,
and we agreed on the contract.
欠陥品を買わせたわけではなく
取引も合意の上だ
If you want to make any more false accusations,
此れ以上変な言いがかりをつけるようなら
I'm willing to go settle this outside.
こっちから出るとこでたらいいんですが
Let's all pitch in
and work together to
make our community great.
We lost...
負けた
Perhaps the best thing to do
would be to consult the police.
ここはやはり警察に相談するのが一番ではないでしょうか
You can't rely on the police for this.
警察はあてにできないわ
He's crooked, but there's a contract,
and we have no proof it was a scam.
インチキとはいえ
契約書はあるし
詐欺だって言う証拠もないし
So there's nothing we can do?
打つ手なしっていうことか
Dammit! How are we
supposed to get 128,000 yen?!
クソ　十二万八千円なんて金額どうすりゃいいんだよ
My apologies, Sire.
申し訳ありません魔王様
I'm partly to blame; I've been
remiss in my duties as guardian.
保護者としての監督不行き届き
私にも責任が
Guardian? Say, how old is Urushihara?
保護者
そういえば漆原って何歳なの？
Pardon?
は
Not in the other world; in Japan.
あっちのじゃなくて　日本での年齢
Oh, I think I made him
eighteen in his official records.
ああ　確か戸籍上は18下 気がする
In that case, I can tell you a good trick.
だったらいい方法を教えてあげてもいいけど
What? Can we get out of
paying the 128,000 yen?
なんだ 12万8千円払わずにすむのか
What is it?!
一体どのような？
"Cooling-Off."
（送货上门销售时，对已签订合同的消费者 在一定期限内可不用支付违约金便能解除合同）
クーリングオフ
A guardian's consent is
required for a minor to sign
未成年者が自分が処分を許された
財産以上の契約行為をするには
any contract for an amount
greater than their allowance.
常に保護者の同意が必要です
Mr. Maou, you're Mr. Urushihara's
recognized guardian...
真奥さんは漆原さんの保護者として認められますので
...so the Cooling-Off Rule applies.
クーリングオフの対象となりますね
Honestly! He completely took us in.
まったく
今回はしてやられましたね
Yeah, that human is sneakier than a demon.
ああ　人間のくせに
悪魔より陰険のことしやがれ
Still, to think Emilia saved us...
しかしエミリアに助けられるとは
She's used to return-happy customers.
クレーマーには慣れっこだからだろう
Gotta get that one on
the demon team someday.
あいつもいずれ魔王組みだな
You jest, Sire.
お戯れを
Are you ready to order?
魔王様　決まりましたか？
Yep, I'll have the same as you.
ああ　俺も同じだ
Two Katsu Doons over here, please!
すみません　カツ丼　二つ
The fingertips plucking
the strings are like the waning moon
爪弾く   指先は欠けた月のよう
拨弄琴弦 指尖如缺月弯弯
A faint light illuminates the world
beyond these dying days
散りゆく 日々の先照らす　微かな灯
微微灯光 投照着似水流年
The music echoes coldly,
and the sound left behind
冷たく   鳴り響きのち残る音に
澄澈清晰 余音在耳旁回响
Is permeated through and
through with more night
遍く     染み込んでく夜の続き
尽染墨色 夜漫漫凭何消遣
The path to the moon, the faint scent,
月へと　　向かう道
温柔月色下的曲径
淡い 匂い 烟った視界の隅
朦胧视线中嗅到花香淡淡
The hazy edges of my vision
I messed up because you said it was simple
単純なんて言うから間違った
并非如你所说的那样天真
Was I crying?
あたしは泣いてた
我已泪流满面
The sky I longed for isn't
quite the color I pictured
憧れた空は描いた色と何処か
憧憬的天空与描绘出的色彩
ちょっと違うけど
虽然有些不同
If I've let my hands fall from my ears,
I'll just keep reaching with them
塞いだ手を離したなら
也要勇敢地伸出双手
差し伸べるまま
不再自欺欺人
It seems I'm formed out of
everything that slips from my grasp
掴めず消えたそのすべてであたしになるという
正是所有的错过造就了现在的我
The only one, all alone
ただ一人の
只属于我
Are you stupid?
馬鹿じゃないの
Emi.
恵美
The Devil, waiting out a red light in
the pouring rain with no umbrella?
魔王が傘も持たずに雨の中で信号待ちなんて
Shut up.
うるせぇ
うん　これ
Here.
I tossed the umbrella I
borrowed from you before, right?
前に借りた傘　捨てちゃったでしょう
I'm replacing it with a new one,
so take it and be grateful.
新しいの返してあげるから
ありがたく受け取りなさい
Huh?
- Just take it!
- Uh, right.
速く取れ
あ はい
Hmph.
Um... thanks.
あのう
ありがとう
You're welcome.
どういたしまして